<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Myolab</title>
    <link>https://myolab.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Myolab</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://myolab.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://myolab.org/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://myolab.org/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;welcome-to-the-myolab&#34;&gt;Welcome to the Myolab&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are a research lab in the Department of Kinesiology at the College of William &amp;amp; Mary.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We study muscle and myosin motors. &lt;em&gt;Myo-&lt;/em&gt; is the greek prefix meaning muscle which forms the basis for many muscle related terms in physiology: &lt;strong&gt;myocyte&lt;/strong&gt; (a muscle cell), &lt;strong&gt;myofilament&lt;/strong&gt; (sarcomere components), and of course, &lt;strong&gt;myosin&lt;/strong&gt; (the motor protein in muscle). Therefore, the interests of the lab is anything &lt;em&gt;myo&lt;/em&gt;-related.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Showcase</title>
      <link>https://myolab.org/showcase/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://myolab.org/showcase/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This article offers a sample of basic Markdown syntax that can be used in Hugo content files, also it shows whether basic HTML elements are decorated with CSS in a Hugo theme.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://myolab.org/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://myolab.org/join/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;interested-in-joining-the-myolab&#34;&gt;Interested in joining the Myolab?&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Feel free to talk to Brent anytime or send an email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bscott@wm.edu&#34;&gt;bscott@&lt;span style=&#34;display:none;&#34;&gt;ignoreme-&lt;/span&gt;wm.edu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please note, the lab is just starting in Fall 2025 and is currently being built. While students are welcome to inquire about joining, the lab is not at full capacity. Student wanting hands-on research experience will get up and running faster in one of the other existing and well-established labs on campus.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wm.edu/as/kinesiology/research/&#34;&gt;There are many fanstasic research labs within the Kinesiology department.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brent Scott</title>
      <link>https://myolab.org/members/brent-scott/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://myolab.org/members/brent-scott/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Brent is an Assistant Professor in the Department of Kinesiology at William &amp;amp; Mary. He teaches courses in Human Health &amp;amp; Physiology and is the principal investigator of the Myolab.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;He was an Exercise Science major at Belmont University (Nashville, TN) before completing his MS and PhD in Kinesiology at UMass Amherst. After graduate school, he completed a post-doctoral research fellowship in Biochemistry &amp;amp; Molecular Biophysics at WashU School of Medicine in St. Louis.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
